J. D. Sloan Photographs MS247
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographic prints and negatives, 1978 -- 2013; MS247.001; 7.4 Linear Feet
  - Tufts Volume 2 860517 to 870517, 1986 -- 1987; MS247.001.001.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Russian Agric/Econ, 1986-06-11; MS247.001.001.00004.00054 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860611-A to 860611-C
    - Mayer & Apatov of USSR solo, 1986-06-10; MS247.001.001.00004.00055 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860610
    - Dental School Walter Brown reception, 1986-06-04; MS247.001.001.00004.00056 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860604-A to 860604-E
    - Tufts XI XIDE/FUDAN Vice President, 1986-05-29; MS247.001.001.00004.00057 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860529-A to 860529-D
    - Tufts Dental, 1986-05-20; MS247.001.001.00004.00058 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860520
    - Commencement 86, 1986-05-18; MS247.001.001.00004.00059 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860518-A 860518-N
    - 860517-A to 860517-W, 1986-05-17; MS247.001.001.00004.00060 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      860517-A to 860517-W
  - Tufts Volume 3 870610 to 880413, 1987 -- 1988; MS247.001.001.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Sackler A
    - Tufts / Sackler School: Second Shoot, 1988-04-13; MS247.001.001.00005.00001 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      880413-A to 880413-F
    - Sackler School, 1988-04-07; MS247.001.001.00005.00002 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      880407-A to 880407-C
    - Tony Cortese Anthony's Pier 4 Dinner, 1988-04-07; MS247.001.001.00005.00003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      880407-D to 880407-F
    - Tufts Employee Recpgnition, 1988-04-06; MS247.001.001.00005.00004 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      880406-A to 880406-F
    - Tufts: Center for Environmental Management, 1988-04-05; MS247.001.001.00005.00005 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      880405-A to 880405-B
    - President's Ball, 1988-03-19; MS247.001.001.00005.00006 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      880319-A to 880319-B
    - Shapiro / Florida, 1988-03-06; MS247.001.001.00005.00007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      880306-A to 880306-H
    - 880305-A to 880305-N, 1988-03-05; MS247.001.001.00005.00008 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      880305-A to 880305-N
    - Tufts Drug Study/ Dr Louis Lasagna 65th Bday, 1988-02-24; MS247.001.001.00005.00009 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      880224-A to 880224-C
      Louis Lasagna
    - Tufts Health Sciences Day, 1988-01-30; MS247.001.001.00005.00010 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      880130-A to 880130-G
    - Tufts Club Xmas Color, 1987-12-22; MS247.001.001.00005.00011 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871222-A to 871222-B
    - Tufts-Vet / Ritz, 1987-12-10; MS247.001.001.00005.00012 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871210-A to 871210-H
      Jeff Chester
    - Al Robatt's Lab, 1987-12-03; MS247.001.001.00005.00013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871203-A to 271203-F
    - 871204, 1987-12-04; MS247.001.001.00005.00014 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871204
    - 871203, 1987-12-03; MS247.001.001.00005.00015 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871203
    - Bookstore, 1987-11-27; MS247.001.001.00005.00016 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871127
    - Tufts: NYC: Tavern on the Green, 1987-11-20; MS247.001.001.00005.00017 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871120-A to 871120-L
    - Tufts / BUA Carpenter, 1987-11-18; MS247.001.001.00005.00018 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871118-A to 871118-B
    - Mrs Cuomo / Tufts Nutrition, 1987-11-17; MS247.001.001.00005.00019 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871117-A to 871117-B
    - Dental M Club, 1987-11-14; MS247.001.001.00005.00020 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871114-A to 871114-J
    - Tufts Med M Dinner @ Four Seasons, 1987-11-06; MS247.001.001.00005.00021 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871106-A to 871106-G
    - Packard Society, 1987-10-30; MS247.001.001.00005.00022 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871030-A to 871030-G
    - Homecoming, 1987-10-31; MS247.001.001.00005.00023 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871031-A to 871031-L
    - Tufts Medical Dr. Wm. Schwartz, 1987-10-29; MS247.001.001.00005.00024 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871029-A to 871029-F
      School of Medicine
    - Tufts Club Robsham @ Pavrotti, 1987-10-25; MS247.001.001.00005.00025 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871025
    - Tufts Vet "M" Club, 1987-10-23; MS247.001.001.00005.00026 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871023-A to 871023-C
    - Mayor of Somerville solo, 1987-10-19; MS247.001.001.00005.00027 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871019
    - Parents Weekend at Tufts, 1987-10-17; MS247.001.001.00005.00028 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871017-A to 871017-G
    - 871016-A to 871016-E, 1987-10-16; MS247.001.001.00005.00029 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      871016-A to 871016-E
    - Tufts Babbitt, 1987-09-30; MS247.001.001.00005.00030 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      870930
    - Tufts Club, 1987-09-28; MS247.001.001.00005.00031 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      870928
    - Quilts Rhoda Cohen, 1987-09-25; MS247.001.001.00005.00032 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      870925
      Rhoda Cohen
    - Tufts Gephard, 1987-09-14; MS247.001.001.00005.00033 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      870914-A to 870914-B
    - Tufts Medical Matriculation, 1987-08-31; MS247.001.001.00005.00034 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      870831-A to 870831-B
    - Dukakis @ Tufts Grafton, 1987-08-04; MS247.001.001.00005.00035 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      870804-A to 870804-F
    - Callow / Rare Book Room, 1987-07-30; MS247.001.001.00005.00036 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      870730-A to 870730-E
    - Aidekman Center for the Arts Groundbreaking, 1987-07-16; MS247.001.001.00005.00037 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      870716-A to 870716-G
    - USSR Doctors Visit on Sackler 8, 1987-07-10; MS247.001.001.00005.00038 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      870710-A to 870710-B
    - Tufts Medical Andrews Professorship award to, 1987-06-27; MS247.001.001.00005.00039 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      870627-A to 870627-J
      School of Medicine; Dr. Richard Cleveland
  - Tufts Volume 4 880414 solo to 881103, 1988-04-14 -- 1988-11-03; MS247.001.002.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Tufts Dental Scholarship, 1988-11-03; MS247.001.002.00001.00001 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881103-A to 881103-C
    - Tufts Dental M, 1988-10-30; MS247.001.002.00001.00002 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881030-A to 881030-F
    - Tufts Packard Society, 1988-10-28; MS247.001.002.00001.00003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881028-A to 881028-G
    - Tufts Chem Engineering Redo, 1988-10-25; MS247.001.002.00001.00004 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881025-A to 881025-D
    - Tufts Engineering ( Gonsalves) gets a grant from A T & T, 1988-10-24; MS247.001.002.00001.00005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881024
      School of Engineering; Gonsalves
    - Tufts Medical M, 1988-10-21; MS247.001.002.00001.00006 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881021-A to 881021-J
    - Engineering ALCOA gives Mah Katchanov a grant, 1988-10-17; MS247.001.002.00001.00007 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881017
    - Vet 10th Anniversary Grafton, 1988-10-16; MS247.001.002.00001.00008 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881016-A to 881016-B
      Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine; Goodall
    - Tufts Vet / 10th Anniv/ Sackler Symp, 1988-10-15; MS247.001.002.00001.00009 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881015-A to 881015-F
    - Tufts Dukakis, 1988-10-11; MS247.001.002.00001.00010 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881011 - A to 881011-D
    - Tufts solo, 1988-10-11; MS247.001.002.00001.00011 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881011
    - Bendetson Hall Dedication & Parents Weekend, 1988-10-01; MS247.001.002.00001.00012 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      881001-A to 881001-G
    - Tufts Ctr Environment Mgt Portraits, 1988-09-29; MS247.001.002.00001.00013 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880929-A to 880929-E
    - TAB 2nd opening, 1988-09-26; MS247.001.002.00001.00014 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880926-A to 880926-C
    - Tufts United Way solo, 1988-09-23; MS247.001.002.00001.00015 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880923
    - Tufts Solo Robert Meserve, 1988-09-22; MS247.001.002.00001.00016 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880922
      Robert Meserve
    - Tufts: Chem Engineering, 1988-09-20; MS247.001.002.00001.00017 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880920-A to 880920-J
    - Tufts Nutrition Computers, 1988-09-02; MS247.001.002.00001.00018 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880902-A to 880902-B
    - Tufts Solo, 1988-09-01; MS247.001.002.00001.00019 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880901
    - Tufts Solo, 1988-08-09; MS247.001.002.00001.00020 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880809
    - Tufts Jumbo Club, 1988-06-01; MS247.001.002.00001.00021 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880601-A to 880601-B
    - Tufts Dental, 1988-05-27; MS247.001.002.00001.00022 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880527-A to 880527-P
    - 880525-A to 880525-E, 1988-05-25; MS247.001.002.00001.00023 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880525-A to 880525-E
    - Kate Philbin: Asbestos Seminar, 1988-05-25; MS247.001.002.00001.00024 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880525-A to 880525-B
      Kate Philbin
    - Tufts Commencement, 1988-05-22; MS247.001.002.00001.00025 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880522-A to 880522-M
    - Walcotts Med School Commencement, 1988-05-22; MS247.001.002.00001.00026 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880522-AA to 880522-GG
    - Tufts Alum Day, 1988-05-21; MS247.001.002.00001.00027 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880521-A to 880521-R
    - Tufts 25th Anniv of Micro and Molecular Biology, 1988-04-29; MS247.001.002.00001.00028 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880429-A to 880429-E
      Peggy Newell
    - Tufts Center for Enviornmental Management, 1988-04-28; MS247.001.002.00001.00029 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880428-A to 880428-E
    - Tufts / Berk Lab, 1988-04-28; MS247.001.002.00001.00030 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880428-T 880428-Z
    - Dental Reunion, 1988-04-23; MS247.001.002.00001.00031 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880423-A to 880423-N
      Lois Shir
    - Tuftonia's Day, 1988-04-19; MS247.001.002.00001.00032 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880419-A to 880419-C
      Gelb
    - Distinguished Service Awards, 1988-04-16; MS247.001.002.00001.00033 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880416-A to 880416-G
      Richardson, Gelb Cicia
    - HNRC 5th Anniversary Nutrition Center, 1988-04-15; MS247.001.002.00001.00034 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880415-A to 880415-G
    - Mayer at Global Information Award solo, 1988-04-14; MS247.001.002.00001.00035 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      880414
  - Tufts Volume 5 881202 to 900328, 1988-12-02 -- 1990-03-28; MS247.001.002.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - " Naming" Brochure, 1989-07-14; MS247.001.002.00002.00001 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890714-A to 890714 E Tags
    - Tufts, 1990-03-28; MS247.001.002.00002.00002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      900328-A to 900328-D
    - Tufts Dental, 1990-02-15; MS247.001.002.00002.00003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      900215-A to 900215-D
    - Tufts: Aidekman Construction, 1990-02-07; MS247.001.002.00002.00004 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      900207-Y to 900207-Z
    - Tufts CEM, 1990-02-07; MS247.001.002.00002.00005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      900207-A to 900207-F
    - Tufts: Packard, 1990-02-03; MS247.001.002.00002.00006 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      900203-A to 900203-I
    - Burdick solo, 1990-02-04; MS247.001.002.00002.00007 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      900204
    - Tufts-CEM / New Director Mr. Moomaw solo, 1990-01-29; MS247.001.002.00002.00008 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      900129
      Moomaw
    - Tufts Armenian Art & Architecture, 1989-11-30; MS247.001.002.00002.00009 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891130-A to 891130-C
    - Tufts Engineering Draper Lab Trio solo, 1989-11-30; MS247.001.002.00002.00010 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891130
    - Medical, 1989-11-27; MS247.001.002.00002.00011 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891127
      Rob Levy
    - Tufts: NYC And Chita Rivera, 1989-11-20; MS247.001.002.00002.00012 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891120-A to 891120-K
    - Tufts, 1989-11-09; MS247.001.002.00002.00013 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891109-A to 891109-C
    - Tufts, 1989-11-08; MS247.001.002.00002.00014 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891108-A to 891108-G
    - Tufts Vet, 1989-10-28; MS247.001.002.00002.00015 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891028-A to 891028-D
    - Tufts: Engineering, 1989-10-22; MS247.001.002.00002.00016 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891022-A to 891022-C
    - Tufts Medical, 1989-10-21; MS247.001.002.00002.00017 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891021-A to 891021-D
    - Tufts Parents Weekend, 1989-10-14; MS247.001.002.00002.00018 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891014-A to 891014-J
      Mary Harris
    - Tufts Dental "M", 1989-10-14; MS247.001.002.00002.00019 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      891014-W to 891014-Z
    - Tufts Manufacturing / Engineering, 1989-09-22; MS247.001.002.00002.00020 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890922-A to 890922-G
    - Toby Wesselhoeft Medical, 1989-08-11; MS247.001.002.00002.00021 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890811-A to 890811-B
      Toby Wesselhoeft
    - Tufts Solo, 1989-07-28; MS247.001.002.00002.00022 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890728
    - Engineering Overseers, 1989-06-27; MS247.001.002.00002.00023 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890627-A to 890627-C
      ( Now Advisors)
    - Student Life Overseers, 1989-06-15; MS247.001.002.00002.00024 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890615
    - Tufts Frame 5, 1989-06-06; MS247.001.002.00002.00025 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890616-Z
    - Tufts Medical Alum in Newport, 1989-06-03; MS247.001.002.00002.00026 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890603-A to 890603-I
    - Tufts Medical Alum in Newport, 1989-06-02; MS247.001.002.00002.00027 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890602-A to 890602-R
    - Tufts Swimmers Alumni Development Party, 1989-06-01; MS247.001.002.00002.00028 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890601-A to 890601-C
    - Tufts Commencement Medical Sackler, 1989-05-21; MS247.001.002.00002.00029 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890521-M to 890521-W
    - Tufts Commencement Extras on Spec, 1989-05-21; MS247.001.002.00002.00030 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890521-AA to 890521-EE
    - Ali Family Library Tufts, 1989-05-19; MS247.001.002.00002.00031 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890519-A to 890519-I
    - Tufts Overseers, 1989-05-18; MS247.001.002.00002.00032 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890518-Y to 890518-Z
      (Now Advisors)
    - Tufts Med Seniors Banquet, 1989-05-17; MS247.001.002.00002.00033 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890517-A to 890517-I
    - Tufts solo, 1989-05-16; MS247.001.002.00002.00034 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890516
    - Tufts: Jeff Summit Torah, 1989-05-07; MS247.001.002.00002.00035 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890507-A to 890507-B
    - Tufts Dental Alum, 1989-04-29; MS247.001.002.00002.00036 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890429-A to 890429-O
    - Tufts Celeste, 1989-04-28; MS247.001.002.00002.00037 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890428-Y to 890428-Z
    - Tufts, 1989-04-28; MS247.001.002.00002.00038 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890428-A to 890428-D
    - Tufts Library for McCardy, 1989-04-26; MS247.001.002.00002.00039 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890426-A to 890426-B
    - Tufts: Celeste Physics/Burlingame, 1989-04-26; MS247.001.002.00002.00040 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890426-X to 890426-Z
    - Tufts: Exper College 25th Anniversary, 1989-04-22; MS247.001.002.00002.00041 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890422-A to 890422-B
    - Pierre Laurent's conference on Greece, 1989-04-21; MS247.001.002.00002.00042 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890421-A to 890421-E
    - Tufts: Distinguished Service Awards, 1989-04-15; MS247.001.002.00002.00043 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890415-A to 890415-E
    - Seniors Awards, 1989-04-08; MS247.001.002.00002.00044 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890408-A to 890408-B
    - Tufts: Employee Recognition, 1989-04-05; MS247.001.002.00002.00045 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890405-A to 890405-E
    - Tufts Celeste, 1989-04-03; MS247.001.002.00002.00046 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890403-A to 890403-B
    - Tufts CEM / 25 yr empl. Recognition, 1989-03-31; MS247.001.002.00002.00047 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890331-A to 890331-G
      Kate Philbin; Dean Cortese; Dr Mayer
    - Tufts Sol Gittleman Portraits, 1989-03-09; MS247.001.002.00002.00048 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890309-A to 890309-E
      Sol Gittleman
    - Tufts: Hotung Café, 1989-03-04; MS247.001.002.00002.00049 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890304-A to 890304-B
      Harry Lightfoot
    - Harry Lightfoot New England College Fund scholarship rec., 1989-02-22; MS247.001.002.00002.00050 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890222-A
      Rick Wetzler
    - Rick Wetzler for CEM, 1989-02-22; MS247.001.002.00002.00051 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890222-B
    - Library Overseers, 1989-02-02; MS247.001.002.00002.00052 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890202
    - Tufts: Radon Night solo, 1989-01-18; MS247.001.002.00002.00053 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890118
    - Dr Rosenberg / HNRC, 1989-01-09; MS247.001.002.00002.00054 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      890109-A
    - Tufts: Center for Enviro Mgmt., 1988-12-13; MS247.001.002.00002.00055 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      881213-A to 881213-C
    - Tufts solo, 1988-12-08; MS247.001.002.00002.00056 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      881208
    - Tufts solo, 1988-12-07; MS247.001.002.00002.00057 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      881207
    - Tufts, 1988-12-02; MS247.001.002.00002.00058 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      881202-A to 881202-C
  - Tufts Volume 6 900403 to 901116, 1990-04-03 -- 1990-11-16; MS247.001.002.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Tufts Medical, 1990-11-16; MS247.001.002.00003.00001 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      9011116-A
    - Tufts Sci Tech Opening, 1990-11-08; MS247.001.002.00003.00002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901108A-901108-B
    - Tufts / NYC, 1990-11-08; MS247.001.002.00003.00003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901108-A to 901108-K
    - Opening of Sci-Tech Center, 1990-11-03; MS247.001.002.00003.00004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901103-A to 901103-L
    - Kids Tour of SciTech, 1990-11-02; MS247.001.002.00003.00005 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901102-A to 901102-F
    - Tufts: Packard Society, 1990-10-27; MS247.001.002.00003.00006 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901027-A to 901027-L
    - Dugger Memorial "track plaque" Celeste, 1990-10-20; MS247.001.002.00003.00007 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901020-A to 901020-F
      Celeste
    - Tufts Dental "M" Celeste, 1990-10-20; MS247.001.002.00003.00008 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901020-G to 901020-O
      School of Dental Medicine; Celeste
    - Dudley "Do" Wright, 1990-10-19; MS247.001.002.00003.00009 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901019-A to 901019-C
    - Tufts Dental, Tufts hosts the ADA, 1990-10-14; MS247.001.002.00003.00010 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901014-A to 901014-E
      School of Dental Medicine; Maria Gove
    - Tufts Parents Weekend, 1990-10-13; MS247.001.002.00003.00011 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901013-A to 901013-G
      Siema
    - Tom Hunt's daughter, 1990-10-11; MS247.001.002.00003.00012 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      901011
    - Tufts Annual Fund, 1990-09-30; MS247.001.002.00003.00013 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900930-A to 900930-C
    - Tufts Veterinary M Club Dinner at Rowes Wharf, 1990-09-27; MS247.001.002.00003.00014 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900927-A to 900927-E
    - Tufts Telefund w/Rosemarie, 1990-09-14; MS247.001.002.00003.00015 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900914-A
      Rosemarie
    - Tufts: Neitle, 1990-09-10; MS247.001.002.00003.00016 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900910-A to 900910-B
    - 900723-A to 900723-B, 1990-07-23; MS247.001.002.00003.00017 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900723-A to 900723-B
    - 900711-A to 900711-B, 1990-07-11; MS247.001.002.00003.00018 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900711-A to 900711-B
    - Tufts Dean Mary Ellen Feinlieb, 1990-07-11; MS247.001.002.00003.00019 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900711-C
    - Tufts Dental "post doc catalog", 1990-07-09; MS247.001.002.00003.00020 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900709-G to 900709-Q
    - Tufts Dental / Dr. Gavel's 90th, 1990-06-28; MS247.001.002.00003.00021 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900628-A to 900628-D
    - CEM Classroom, 1990-06-26; MS247.001.002.00003.00022 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900626-A to 900626-D
      Beth Harding
    - Tufts Sackler 10th Anniversary, 1990-06-22; MS247.001.002.00003.00023 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900622-A to 900622-G
      Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences: Peggy Newell
    - Tufts Medical Dean Bank retires, 1990-06-15; MS247.001.002.00003.00024 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900615-A to 900615-I
    - Tufts Medical Alumni Weekend, 1990-05-31; MS247.001.002.00003.00025 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900531-A to 900531-O
    - Zuckers @ Rowes Wharf Solo, 1990-05-30; MS247.001.002.00003.00026 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900530
    - Sackler School color, 1990-05-24; MS247.001.002.00003.00027 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900524-F to 900524-G
    - Sackler, 1990-05-24; MS247.001.002.00003.00028 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900524-A to 900524-E
    - Callow farewell, 1990-05-23; MS247.001.002.00003.00029 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900523-A to 900523-D
    - Tufts Medical Senior Banquet ( shot by Tim Burdick), 1990-05-16; MS247.001.002.00003.00030 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900516-A to 900516-G
    - Olin Building Cornerstone, 1990-05-04; MS247.001.002.00003.00031 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900504-A to 900504-C
    - Track Dedication " Ding" Dusseault Celeste, 1990-04-28; MS247.001.002.00003.00032 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900428-A to 900428-D
    - Arts Overseers, 1990-04-25; MS247.001.002.00003.00033 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900425-Y to 900425-Z
    - Tufts 90 Dental Reunion, 1990-04-21; MS247.001.002.00003.00034 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900421-A to 900421-O
    - Tufts: 50 Baseball, Duffett etc. Senior Awards, 1990-04-21; MS247.001.002.00003.00035 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900421-V to 900421-Z
    - Tufts, 1990-04-19; MS247.001.002.00003.00036 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900419-A to 900419-E
    - Tufts Employee Recognition Luncheon, 1990-04-03; MS247.001.002.00003.00037 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      900403-A to 900403-D
      contact sheets; Medford Campus
    - 880522-A to 880522-M, 1988-05-22; MS247.001.002.00003.00038 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Prince of Asturias, 1994-05-18; MS247.001.002.00003.00039 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      940518-A to 940518-F
      Jose Alvarez
    - Tufts: Mayer Chair, 1994-05-04; MS247.001.002.00003.00040 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      940504-A to 940504-F
    - Renaming of USDA to Mayer Center, 1994-09-16; MS247.001.002.00003.00041 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      940916-A to 940916-E
  - Tufts 1994, MS247.001.002.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Tufts Medical Jaharis Chair, 1994; MS247.001.002.00004.00001 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      010405-A to 010405-H
    - Tufts Medical Friedman Chair Andrew Levey, MD, 1994; MS247.001.002.00004.00002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      010412-A to 010412-J
      Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy; Andrew Levey, MD
    - Berger Chair Dinner, 1994-05-09; MS247.001.002.00004.00003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940509-A to 940509-D
    - 940507-A to 940507-Y, 1994-05-07; MS247.001.002.00004.00004 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940507-A to 940507-Y
      Carol Boulter
    - Tufts: Engineering 100th, 1994-05-14; MS247.001.002.00004.00005 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940514-A to 940514-G
    - Tufts Medical Commencement, 1994-05-22; MS247.001.002.00004.00006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940522-A to 940522-P
      School of Medicine; T. Berry Brazelton
    - Prof. Thornton gets Dana Award, 1994-02-24; MS247.001.002.00004.00007 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940224-A to 940224-B
    - Tufts Dental Alumni Weekend, 1994-04-30; MS247.001.002.00004.00008 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940430-A to 940430-AA
    - Tufts Health Sci "M" Club at JFK, 1994-10-22; MS247.001.002.00004.00009 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941022-A to 941022-J
    - Center for Study of Drug Development Directors Meeting, 1994-05-26; MS247.001.002.00004.00010 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940526-A to 940526-D
      Toni Snow
    - Restorative Dental Brochure, 1994-10-04; MS247.001.002.00004.00011 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941004-A to 941004-C
      School of Dental Medicine; Dan Quinn; Pat McGarry
    - Tufts: Fletcher First 94 catalogue shoot, 1994-04-12; MS247.001.002.00004.00012 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940412-A to 940412-N
      Related Materials
      Paul Bauer
    - Tufts Club Annual Meeting, 1994-10-11; MS247.001.002.00004.00013 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941011-A to 941011-B
      Chris Gogen
    - Grace Mitchell Luncheon, 1994-10-13; MS247.001.002.00004.00014 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941013-A to 941013-B
    - Tufts: Fletcher Dean Sheehan, 1994-06-24; MS247.001.002.00004.00015 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940624-A to 940624-B
      Dean Sheehan
    - Tufts: Dental Parents, 1994-03-25; MS247.001.002.00004.00016 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      940325-A to 940325-D
    - Tufts Club Career Networking, 1994-11-07; MS247.001.002.00004.00017 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      941107-A to 941107-B